Where did you come from, flubber?
"Hello, Hal."
I'm so full of bacon, my body's meant for shakin'
And when I start to wiggle, my nipples, they will jiggle
Once again I have to be embarrassed for the both of us. Yep!
You go straight for your job after school today.
I don't want you to be late for your first day of work. And no excuses!
I don't wanna hear, "A lion escaped from the zoo",
or, "The bus driver went insane and refused to stop."
Francis's friend gave Reese a job at the Circus Burger.
It's perfect.
Reese gets to be bossed around all day
by the only guy on the planet that's dumber than he is.
- This job is stupid! - You do get to wear a paper hat.
Reese, you wanna drive when you get your license,
you have to pay your own insurance!
Yeah, but everyone else has insurance! Why do I need it?
They've got it covered.
Son, it's not as simple as that. You see...
Good morning, everybody! Say good morning, Charlie.
Show everyone how alive you are.
My parents made a deal with Dewey.
If he keeps his goldfish alive for two months, he gets a dog.
- Am I doing a good job? - You sure are.
- How is that fish still alive? - I don't know
He never feeds it and he leaves it out in the sun for hours.
Last week there was an old banana peel in there!
I do not want a dog in this house!
As long as the fish is alive, there is nothing we can do about it.
Hal, I expect you to take care of this.
- What are you suggesting? - I'm not suggesting anything.
I just want it taken care of.
Class, today we begin a new round of independent study projects.
Hydrostatic equilibrium?
My God, I am still my Path integral quantisation
My stepdad's right,I'm useless.
Well, the cold, hard fact of life
is some are more advanced than others.
Some even think they're more advanced than me.
I never said that.
Yet you assume I'm talking about you.
You're looking right at me!
I'm sure you're all convinced by virtue of you being in this class,
your intellects tower above those of
tiny plebeians wasting oxygen in the rest of the school.
But, to some, you are nothing more
than howling primates.
I'm excited to announce today
that we're welcoming to our class a new student.
A young man of unparalleled intellect.
As near as we can measure, his IQ is over 280.
Those tests are culturally biased!
Think what you will.
Your petty fears no longer concern me.
I finally have the mental clay worthy of my sculpting.
Barton is a white-hot comet of brilliance,
blazing through our dark little corner of ignorance.
A mind of such unfathomable reach
- and enormous power. - Can I come in now?
Barton, I thought I told you to wait till you heard,
"A new era for man."
But there's a bee out there.
So, assistant manager. How's that happen?
INS raid, Quendus out.
So, from 12 to 5, Monday, Wednesday, Thursday,
this is my domain.
I'm proof you don't need to graduate high school.
That's just propaganda
from those money-grabbing diploma companies.
Sean, Doug, this is Reese.
- Hey. what's up? - Hey.
OK. Press cow for burger, potato for fries.
And I'm not sure what this is.
Does that look like a pig or a dog to you?
Wouldn't it be easier to put words on the keys?
Ah, a man of letters.
A word to the wise.
I wouldn't throw that in anyone's face.
Once you get your total, you put the money in the drawer,
except you are making a pocket transactions. What's that?
Kind of a morale builder.
Once in a while take 5 or 10 bucks.
but you don't ring it up, put it in your pocket instead.
You don't have a problem with that, do you?
Oh, no. That's cool.
See, Reese. You've entered the working world.
A world of adult responsibility.
I have the key to her locker.
If you wanna smell her jacket later, just let me know.
Hey, they found the last piece of that guy.
Oh, man!
Come on, guys. We talked about this.
If we're gonna share a roll of toilet paper,
can we at least keep it on the spindle?
As long as you are bringing this kinda of stuff up,
I got a fiancee coming Thursday.
Fiancee? What are you taking about? I'm engaged.
It comes to time when a man gets tired of playing the field.
What field? You don't even know any women.
That occurred to me, too,
That's why I ordered one from Russia.
A mail-order bride? That actually exists?
Sure. In some of the more irradiated parts of former Soviet Union,
there are a lot of marriage-minded women.
That's my darling Svetlana.
Wait a second. Yep.
Svetlana.
How come you're driving us to school?
Because that's what moms do sometimes.
Argh!
OK, you know your Tolstoy and your Eliot...
Let's see how you do with the Bard.
"Every true man's apparel fits your thief."
Measure For Measure, Act 4, Scene 2.
Elbow says to Pompey.
Could you hand me my green crayon?
- Wow, he's right again. -  OK, Barton
let's try Chaucer's The Shipman's Tale.
- Should I start with the prologue? - Please. How about line 203?
"And when your husband has gone off to Flanders,"
"I shall deliver you from fear of slanders,"
"and on the word he caught her by the flanks"
"and clasped her closely, giving her a riot of kisses,"
"saying softly, 'Keep things quiet'"
What are you doing?
Chaucer? I cannot believe you're polluting his mind
with such pop culture drivel!
I apologise for them, Barton.
I'll do everything I can to minimise these annoying distractions
so that you can concentrate on the accelerated programme
I've laid out for you.
Together we are gonna astonish the world.
Would you like a pixy stix?
Thank you.
Having problems, Malcolm?
No, no, not you
It's the stupid hydrostatic equilibrium. It doesn't make sense!
It is awfully difficult. But don't despair.
I'm here for you, Malcom.
I'll make sure you get the help you deserve.
To estimate the pressure at the centre of the sun,
just assume a constant density of 1.41 grams per cubic cm.
Am I going too fast for you?
You know, Herkabe only made you my tutor to humiliate me.
I thought it was to humiliate me.
I don't understand why is this so hard?!
Don't give up. Remember The Little Engine That Could?
You're not listening!
I get everything!
In my entire life, there is nothing I haven't been able to master.
I took algebra in 6th grade!
I taught my dad how to rebuilt his transmission when I was five!
I was reading before I could walk!
I remember my own birth. What?!
D'you know your heart stops during your mother's contractions?
You seriously remember that?
Worst was the diaper changing.
That was the most degrading week of my life.
So, what's it like in there?
What do you mean?
Well, your brain?
I mean, for me it's like, when I'm thinking really hard,
my brain starts making all these connections.
Those connections make other connections,
Everything starts to moving really fast.
Then it feels like a bomb's going off.
Is yours like that?
It's more like a beehive.
And every bee has a brain like yours.
OK, ready!
That is so cool!
I wish you had a gun
so we can really test this out.
Excuse me. Can I get some help here?
Hi, Greg.
So I overheard your mom talking on the phone
and it's true. You've got a job.
I applied here once. Didn't get it.
- It's all politics. - I guess.
- So what do you want? - I want you to listen very carefully.
My blood sugar's dangerously low
so I don't wanna burn up calories repeating myself.
I want the jumbo clown burger with big top fries,
no pickles, a slice of onion, make sure it's centre cut,
and extra tomatoes.
And let's do the pattie well on one side, medium on the other.
Make sure they open a fresh package for my bun.
If it's stale I bail.
Seriously.
Your total's $5.45 and you get free refills on the soda.
Heard that one before. Turns out it's just for today.
What a sack!
That's a pocket transaction if I ever saw one.
Oh, yeah. Right.
Artie, you put together one hell of a bachelor party.
I'm much obliged to you.
I'm just sorry the nearest stripper's 300 miles away.
Hey, how's she doin' anyway?
She took her top off!
Oh, yeah!
Listen up! I'd like to say a few words about my mate Pete,
on account of his upcoming nuptials.
Many's the time, when I've been feeling low,
and I always knew I could turn to Pete.
He'd be lying on his bunk, trimming his beard with a lighter,
and I'd think, "Hell, I'm better than that."
To Pete and his lucky lady!
What's going on with you?
I just don't get what are we celebrating?
I mean, it just seems wrong.
It's Pete's life.
If he wants to marry a total stranger, that's his business.
What about this woman? Is anyone thinking about her?
Right now I'm trying to keep a topless stripper in my head.
I don't have room for much else.
Think about it for a second.
She's blindly committing
to spend her life in this god forsaking place
with Pete as her husband.
What kind of poor creature would actually go through with this?
Maybe her life's pretty awful.
Worse than this?
What? Does she live in a slaughterhouse?
Is she dragged to work by horses every day?
She couldn't possibly know what she's getting into.
You're exaggerating. We don't know.
It might work out fine.
Dude, how's business?
Where were you? I was supposed to be home for dinner
but you are the only one who can cash me out.
Hey, I'd stay on my good side if I was you.
One of these days somebody'll have to clean these bathrooms.
Whoa, this is way uncool.
Reese, you can't take this much money.
What are you talking about?
Your cash drawer, man.. It is over $400 bucks short. Look.
The whole point is to take five or ten bucks. That's it.
You got to put the 400 back.
I didn't take it. Honest.
Dude. It's your register.
- Did he give his register key to anyone today? - No.
I didn't take it. I didn't take any.
I never even do one of those stupid pocket transactions.
What do you talking about? I saw you yesterday.
No, I wanted it to look like I was taking it. But I didn't really.
When you guys weren't looking I put the money back.
You guys didn't see it cos I was being... sneaky and stuff.
Nice, Reese.
- Way to screw it up for everybody. - I didn't take it!
Look, man. If you are thinking that I'm coverin' for you, you are crazy.
When the owner comes back tomorrow morning and checks the books,
that money better be herel, or you're going down.
Alright. The change from apparent to absolute magnitude in all spectra
The formula is...
A over B times K over D. That's if K is...
How do they expect you to learn all these formulas?
Use a mnemonic device,
like Enephru, Babashar, Kalar, Dastrer.
Babylonian kings, Third Dynasty.
Stop complaining. I have homework, too.
Ah, it's a butterfly.
Malcolm, you got to help me.
- What's goin' on? - It's horrible.
There is $400 missing from my register during my shift,
and they think I took it.
- Well, did you? - No, of course not!
- I'm Barton. - Who's this dork?
- He is my tutor. - You're kiddin' me!
The one time I need you to be a genius
I find you've been faking the whole smart thing.
Reese, calm down. How did this happen?
I don't know.
My register didn't total up right at the end of the shift.
- Who was there? - Everyone.
Me, Sean, Greta, Richie.
Richie? Why didn't you say so at the first place?
What do you mean?
It's Richie. He's setting you up.
How do you know?
Because it's Richie! C'mon!
Barton, you wanna learn something about the real world?
- Not really. - Too bad.
You're coming.
Dewey, you have to cover it for us.
Make sure it sounds like we're all still here.
Got it.
Ow! Stop it!
You shut up!
Stupid creeps!
Ow! Stop it!
- Did you get it? - Yes, I got it.
Pet store owner told me it was already dead,
but I suspect the worst.
OK. Let's switch the fish tonight when Dewey's sleeping.
I don't know, Lois. It seems so sneaky and underhanded.
What kind of example are we setting for the boys?
Well, Hal, stop worrying.
The boys are fine.
Hey dude, did you get the money?
Yeah, you'd like another 400, wouldn't you?
What are you talking about?
Wow! An entire colony of parasitica.
Get your own pizza, Dewey.
His name's not Dewey.
How come you had me call him that all these years?
Look. We know you took the money
and you're trying to pin it on Reese.
After everything my brother's done for you!
All the alibis, all the handouts,
- all the times he's helped you fake your death! - Whoa! Dudes!
I wasn't even there today.
The only time I came in was to cash out.
You were right there.
Yeah, but I had a ten-minute break at 4:30.
You could have snuck in then and take the money.
- Yeah, but... - You wanna play innocent?
Fine. We'll just let the police decide.
Whoa, police.!
What makes you think the cops are gonna take your side?
Maybe cos you've been arrested like 10 times for petty theft.
Excuse me, one of those was for arson.
I am telling you, you're making a big mistake.
- No, I'm not! - Yes, you are!
- No, I'm not! - Yes, you are.
He didn't do it. According to this citation,
Richie was stopped at 4:20 at 18th and Wilson
for urinating from a moving vehicle.
- So? - So the Circus Burger is on Walnut,
which is at least 25 miles away.
He couldn't have got there during Reese's break.
Well what if the traffic was light..
Yeah. And maybe if a '78 Bonneville could go 300 miles an hour.
Otherwise, it's impossible.
Hey, way to go, Dewey!
- Let me see that. - Is he right?
Yes. He's always right.
Sorry, Richie. Come on, Reese, let's go.
But I swear to God, I didn't do it. I didn't take the money!
Well, look. We still have a few hours.
Maybe we can figure...
Richie, I got us this DVD player
but we need to steal another 600
if you want the surround...
..sound.
You may wanna hang on to that receipt.
I can't believe you lied!
We are calling the cops!
Hey-ey-ey. Maybe we could figure out some sort of a deal?
Whatever you guys want, it's yours.
We get to use your place for a party any time we want.
Yeah, and we get free burgers for life.
I get to make out with your girlfriend.
Forget it!
Alright, the bean bag chair.
Wow! Pete, is that really you?
No, it's a reflection.
Here. You can give these to Svetlana.
Eric and Artie should be back any minute with your bride.
I gotta to be honest, I'm er... I'm a little nervous.
You are about to marry a total stranger.
Have you really thought about what you're doing?
I've been thinking about settling down for a long long time.
But you don't know anything about her.
What if she thinks you're...
What if she doesn't like you?
I'd be sad
but I'd reassure her I'd support her anyway,
cos I made that commitment.
Then I guess I'd spend the rest of my life being sweet to her.
And also changing her mind.
- Well, good luck, Pete. - Thanks.
Svetlana's here, and she is gorgeous!
I must've misread the catalogue.
Just look how light on her feet she is.
- Hey, baby. - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, guys.
Oh, hey, Pete...
Just get that thing out of here!
- I'll take care of it. - I got it.
- Why you? Cos I signed for it!
Who cares if you signed for it? Wait a minute.
That's our ride.
How nice of Richie to drive you to school.
Yeah, well, that's just his way of saying, "thanks for a job well done."
Good morning, everybody.
Now, son, don't be disappointed...
Say good morning, Charlie.
Show everyone how alive you are!
Aren't I doing a good job?
Yeah, yeah. Great.
That little monster!
He's been buying his own fish and switchin' 'em!
God only knows how many he's gone through.
- He's gonna pay for this! - How?
If we bust him, he'll know we've been cheating, too.
Dewey, your father and I are so proud of
the way you've taken care of that fish.
Yes, we are. You certainly proved to us you can be trusted.
It's so nice to have a boy
who's so conscientious, responsible
and honest and who always finds a way to do the right thing.
Before we go any further, is there anything you wanna tell me?
I want a beagle!
You're not gonna get it, you little sneak!
We know that you've been switching fish on us,
and that's because I put a dead fish in there last night!
That's cheating! You're cheaters!
It's not exactly textbook
but at least we're not getting a dog.
I cleaned out my cubby.
You're sure I can't talk you into staying?
Mom says I need a healthier environment.
She thinks it's creepy the way you're using me
for your own self-grandiosement.
A healthier environment? That's not what you need.
Son, you'll never connect normally with another human being.
People will recognise your brilliance and loathe you for it.
The best you can hope for is uncomprehending fear
which I can channel into great things.
- Please? - Can I go now?
Sure. Go.
You, my ex-wife,
all of my therapists, you're all the same.
Bye, guys.
Bye, Barton.
Good luck at NASA.
Send us a letter when you get declassified.
Mr Herkabe, we know this is hard for you, so...
It's his dad.
We photo-shopped your head in.