I am home
Hi honey
we are on our own tonight,I thought maybe we go out to dineer
Where are the kids?
Malcolm is over Stevie's Reese's got a hockey practice
Dewey's at Billy's or one of the neighborhood kids
So we are on our own
What do you in the mood for?
That is gotta be a new record
people are always asking our class to volunteer for stuff
They just assume we are social rejects with nothing better to do
And it's true
I just don't like any thrown on my face
So our school needs a kid about your age to be in our school play
We are a lot of fun!
The play is by a guy named William Shakespeare
He was a writer way back in olden times
He was a syphilitic drunk fronting
for the 14th Earl of Oxford
Why can not you leave the part alone!
So he didn't have the benefit of higher education
How many Phd is the great King Lear
now now try to remember we have a guest
Let's save our heated words for our open forum Friday
Megan continue
Whoever he was
He had a pointed litter beard
and he wrote a really good play called "MidSummer Nights Dream"
We need someone to play the changeling boy
Okay before anyone gets too excited there is a downside
- you'll probablely have to miss class - I will do it!
He can't! We were working on a secret project that
I've said too much
Okay, I thought we agree, no more secret projects
Some of you still don't have your eyebrows back from your last secret project
- I can do both - All right
Just as long as you know your where your priorities are
I can go now
I used to think she was so
boring but after she's bi-curious she's just so much I don't know cooler
Oh my God! That is so true!
She's like totally changed the personalities she's been wheat
Oh, and have you heard?
Mark is totally out of that swing thing which is so over, and into goth...
oh!
I read that That's really a good book
That's Travis. He has angst
Look at all these people!
They are pierced.They are brooding.They are wearing wired clothes
They don't care about anything!
It's like a room full of Francises
Okay, people!
We are doing the Act 3 scene 2
Oberon, Puck
- Where's My Puck? - I think he has a wrestling meet.
Hey, you!
Changeling boy
- Can you read? - Yeah
we gotta half these kids beat
Read Puck for the day page 27
This is thy negligence:
still thou mistakest
Or else committ'st thy knaveries wilfully
Believe me, king of shadows, I mistook
Did not you tell me I should know
The man by the Athenian garment be had on?
And so far blameless proves my enterprise,
That I have nointed an Athenian's eyes and so far
You went from a part
with no lines to the lead in a high school play?
That's great! That's not musical is it?
- No - That's great!
Dude you play a fairy!
Not just any fairy Reese! He's the biggest fairy in a whole play!
I'm so proud of you
rehearsals are every night. You have to get me there by 5
Every night?
oh, yeah we build sets on the weekends
Okay we can do this
if I go to work early I can get off in enough time to drop you off at rehearsals
before I take Reese to hockey
except the days Reese is detention
And then Dewey is home alone
I'll it take care of it, I can rearrange my schedule for a couple of weeks
It'll be fun spending some time together
Can we run over things the car like we did last time?
It was already dead
This is your best guacamole yet, Joe
Thanks
The secret is fresh lime juice
Commander on the floor
no, please. Don't let me disturb you
make yourselves at home
Wait a minute
This is not your home
This is not your Mama's house
There is no maid here to clean up your toys
And yet, I look around this institution of learning
I see video games. I see girlie magazines
and I see Garth
Garf Vader, defiling our Wall of remebering
Well clearly things have got a little lax around here
I blame myself, but it is you who will suffer
From now on there will be weekly inspections
and you will relinquish all nonstandard-issue personal
affects and artwork
It's time for you to learn that true happiness comes from within
So why you are so happy sir?
I'm as giddy as a Schoolgirl, Cadet
Okay， get each other cleaner, glitter for Malcolm's costume
I think that's it
Oh my god! Is that right?
- What time do you have? - 5:45
5:45
That's not possible I
Dropped off Malcolm, picked up Reese. Dinner is in the oven
What is it?
I have the next 25 minutes free
How did you manage that? Did you leave a kid somewhere?
no. They are all accounted for
- What do you gonna do? - I don't know
I don't know
- So this goes here? - Yeah, that should do it
hey, these were in English
this is nice, never looks like the box when I do it alone
Me either
We make a good team
All right, you start on the main street I'll do university place.
we'll meet in the bistro say noon-ish
- Would you like a massage? - I Don't know
- I'm really not a massage person - It only takes 15 minutes
Well
I do have some to time to kill
I am not taking off my shirt
and I am warning you, I never been hypnotized and I never been relaxed
actually feels
feels
pretty good
Pleading for a lover's fee
Shall we their fond pageant see
Lord, what fools these mortals be
I'm very upset with you Malcolm
You made me care again
- Malcolm that was terrific! - God I give anything to be as good as you!
And if you are this good now
imagining how amazing you're gonna be when you are 15
and think how cute he's gonna be when he is 15
oh my god, did I just giggle?
Did you just giggle
"Stevie, what are you doing here?
You missed the meeting
You jeopardize
ing
our project
Great, see you in class
I wonder if I could just go straight  to high school?
I've been told skipping grades stunts you socially
but I think I've been lied to
But sir, that's a photo of my sister!
To you she is your sister. to the others cadets, she is a distraction
Now, if you need me to go into more detail on that. I will
How long are those sideburns Cadet?
This is crazy!
Even prisoners can have photographs
Spangler trying to take away the things that remind us we're still human
Francis, don't rock the boat
I don't care anymore
It's time to take last desperate stand for individualality and freedom
Malcolm, Reese. Get a move on
Oh good god Hal! When do you gonna clean this up?
Malcolm Reese, let's go!
Honey, I promised Dewey I'd spend time with him
This must have cost a fortune!
We'll talk about this later
Some of us have places to be!
So Dewey, I believe our little community can use a school
We don't need it, everyone borns smart
Oh, it's beautiful son. It's Utopia
and anyone stupid will be ground for food
Ah
A cannibal utopia
Interesting
Oh you are still here?
I was just doing some shopping and
I thought, while I'm was here. You know
I step over and say hi
Oh, my god. How do you that?
this releases the mind
This releases the heart
And you know what this one does?
We need to talk
You missed our last 5 secret meetings
and our text run is in less than 20 minutes
Why do you hate us?
Guys, I don't hate you
I've just been really busy
We're still friends
- Really? - Of cause
So you are not bailing on the project?
- No! - Then you have the final figures!
Yeah, I worked on them all night after rehearsal they're on my desk
Here
It was the other kids who doubt you
Hey Malcolm. Need a ride?
I gotta go
She's distracted We have to do it now!
The program is running
Let's light this candle
Ignition
in
Blast off
It's trajectory seems rather peculiar
Okay, there are any number reasons  why that might have gone wrong.
Where is it?
I work hard too, but I manage to make it to Lamaze class
We had a vote
we want you get rid of the plant.
You can't get us all the troubles with this little sunny use
This isn't a stunt. This is an act of violence
It's a plant!
Can't you see. It isn't about a plant
It's about fighting tyranny fascist and oppression!
When Spangler sees this
He'll know he didn't crash our spirit and he never will
It's not worth the risk
Once again it seems like I'm the only man around here
I can't believe Nicole wearing dress like that
you can only see her nipple. If she wants to be a slut that's fine
- But don't make me lose my lunch - I know,
she's like totally trying to impress David
But the way he's off in Brenda's business she didn't have a chance
I can't believe how deep our conversations are getting
You never gonna believe what I heard about Josh. But you can't tell anyone
I overheard his stepsister
When I was in the bathroom - His half sister or step sister
No, his step sister. That's why he can  have a crush on her
- They were just talking about me weren't they? - No, we are talking about Josh
Oh my god! His father like totally went down
after catching him in the hot tub with his step sister
but you know what I don't even think he knows the whole story
That's my cue
I feel guilty having so much fun and at ditching the Krelboynes
but I'm sure they are doing fun without me
You boys just lucky no one call the police
You can't prove there's any correlation between our rocket exploding
and Caroline giving birth at the parking lot
She and the baby are fine. Thanks for asking
And
Rocket?
Oh god that is true
It's finished
A perfect society
We have done what 5 thousand years of so called civilization couldn't do
We create a world at works
we?
You wanna destroy it don't you?
Yeah
Well I appreciate that you haven't
You've shown a lot of restraint
Here, Enjoy
Oh dear, I know we gotta a little carried away but this is it, I promise
- It's okay, I'm going grocery shopping - Did't you just go grocery shopping ?
Yeah sure, no problem
- Thank you - Where is Mr. Lee?
- Excuse me? - The massages guy, where is he?
Oh, he's not working here any more
What do you mean? That's impossible! He would never leave without telling me
Well I can trying to find out where he move to
so he can leave me again
Forget it!
it's over
I heard John has a new piercing
and I'll give you three guesses where and it's not ear or belly  belly
Julie would know, she went camp with one of her boyfriend with out town
John takes all the girl camping and he's trying to  convince them to go skinny-dipping
But I don't think John's naked will turn me up guys forever
You know, we should totally do
We should totally have a pool party night half on Saturday
- Malcolm want to go? - Yeah!
wait, I have something to do on Saturday
Oh yeah, the play
live, live
Die
live, live, live live
hey, what happened to the
judicial system presided over by a tribunal of wise elders
I had 'em lined up and shot
- You know son, maybe you've been spent to much - Silence! Seize him
All right son, I think it's time you goose-stepped off to bed
you're embarrassing me in front of my men
Hal
Hal!
Why is this still here?
No fair! You did without me?!
Spangler's coming lose the plant
Time has come, we'll drawn the line
This is our Alamo
It's a bad example but you know what I mean
Attention
This is more like it
Everything shipshape the commanding officer enters
and is greeted by straightened backs
And cracker of shoe leather
Now I know it's been a rough couple of days
but we'll agree we are the better for it
We are a leaning meaning learning machine
Now I know that some of you think I'm a sadist
but some day you'll thank me
Man, that's brutal
Is there anything we can do to cheer you up?
Do you have more pictures of your sister?
I give him curses, yet he gives me love
Hal, please stop. You're making it worse
You okay, sport
Why are we here? Malcolm betrayed us
if you love something, let it go
save your cat poster philosophy for someone else
We're taking
the highroad
But you were totally scamming together
No. We were just smacking
She claims she was just "hanging out" with Andrew at the party
but they were really hooking up.
I can not believe she would
Enough. Hold, or cut both strings
Was that my cue? Quick, lower me.
This must be one of those times when it feels like an eternity
but only a few seconds have gone by.
How com Malcolm didn't say anything in 5 minutes?
Line
Normally I would enjoy something like that but this is just sad
How now, spirit? Wither wander you?
The King doth keep his revels here tonight.
So, good night unto you all.Give me your hands if we be friends
and Robin shall restore amends.
It's over? You promised a partial nudity
Yeah that was a lie
And ice cream after?
that too
How now, spirit? Wither wander you?
The King doth keep his revels here tonight.
I knew I knew it!